[Music]
ah
wasp wasp gooey
gooey go away
okay we're fine we're fine we're fine
hi everyone i hope you're doing well
if you've been watching the news you
probably know
that my area has been going through a
heat wave
for the last few days
it's probably going to continue for a
little while more
to give you a sense of what kind of heat
wave this is the highest so far
recorded has been 115
degrees one afternoon i grew up in
a few different tropical places and
i was used to warmer weather but but
nothing like this
this the high temperatures compounded
with the dryness of this
area and the really hard sun there's no
island breezes
like in cuba or puerto rico so it it
definitely
just beats down on you all this
happening
made me decide that a
video this week just wasn't feasible for
me
so obviously i'm still making a video
but it's very different from what i
usually do
the videos i make take much of the week
to create
but i did want to let you know that we
are all
safe and sound um despite everything
going on
mr darcy is doing just fine he's at my
mother's house with a huge
fan right in front of him just blasting
him and he's very very happy
and my dog is also over there and and
he's doing better now too and we've been
taking a lot of trips to the river
so i'm sure by next week things are
going to be a little more
back to normal and i'll be able to make
some videos
but yeah it it felt right to let you
guys know what's going on
of course i did want to be able to share
at least something with you
and i thought this would be a great
opportunity to share
a few clips and moments and memories
from this year i've gathered so far
and share them with you and they're
little clips
and things that we i've never been able
to find a way to put into a video
but they're very special or beautiful
moments and so
i will follow this little segment of me
talking with those videos
[Music]
so
you